#### CONTACT



07975 697134



jackdomleo7@hotmail.com



https://jackdomleo.dev



28 Melksham Road, Nottingham, UK NG5 5RX

### SKILLS

- → Basic knowledge of Adobe Creative Cloud software including Photoshop, Illustrator and Acrobat
- → Confident in working with SEO and identifying key ideas to help improve organic and paid SEO
- → Competent in working in an agile environment to collaborate, develop and test ideas, bugs and new features
- → Confident in using and developing web applications using different programming languages, frameworks and IDE's. I have experience with:
  - HTML 5, Twig HTML,
     Bootstrap 4, Grav CMS
  - o CSS 3, Sass/SCSS, LESS
  - JavaScript, jQuery, React JS, Electron JS
  - o C# and Python
  - Git, Command Line and Markdown
  - IDE's such as JetBrains, Visual Studio and VS Code
  - Project management systems such as DevOps and Flow
  - Google services such as Cloud, Search Console and Analytics
  - o Mailchimp

# Jack Domleo

Junior Web Developer

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an energetic and enthusiastic person with experience working in a small IT team and a larger development team with experience working in an agile and waterfall environment. My present career aim is to progress in web/software development developing programs as a team and individually using services such as Microsoft Azure and Google Cloud. I enjoy a challenge and will tackle anything thrown at me. I enjoy the environment of working in IT and I find the development work interesting and satisfying. The opportunity to learn new skills and work with new technologies is particularly attractive to me.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Junior Developer

March 2019 - Present

Mitrefinch, Nottingham (& York)

As a Junior Developer in this software company, my responsibilities include:

- Taking the lead on the stylesheets of the redesign of Mitrefinch's products using SCSS to make the styles as simple but effective as possible.
- Learning the C# programming language
- Learning to work in an agile environment
- Having the opportunity to travel to their head office in York to meet the rest of the team

I am learning new skills every day and am eager to learn more.

# IT Developer Apprentice

Sept 2018 - Feb 2019

flybmi, East Midlands Airport

As an IT Developer Apprentice for this airline, my responsibilities included:

- Worked towards BCS Level 3 in Software Development
- Developed new programs from a design specification using frameworks such as Bootstrap 4, Grav CMS, Core UI and Electron JS
- Created new templates using Twig HTML that can be accessed via the Grav CMS and maintaining the content on the flybmi.com website

During my time at flybmi, I gained 6 months' worth of knowledge and experience working in the airline industry and working together with other employees to develop an end product.

Reason for leaving: Company filed for administration



Jon Mennell
Delivery Team Lead
Mitrefinch
jon.mennel@mitrefinch.co.uk



Tim Moore Head of IT flybmi 07503 914916 timjimmoore@gmail.com



George Smith Digital Systems Manager flybmi 07415 371200

#### HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- → Walking
- → Travelling & Days Out
- → Nottingham Panthers Ice Hockey games

# ACHIEVEMENTS

- → Young Enterprise
  - Appointed as
    Managing and Finance
    Director for our team
- → Air Cadet Organisation
  - Completed NNAS, basic first aid and radio communication courses
- → Bronze & Silver DofE
  - Required teamwork, communication and survival skills
- → Black Belt
  - Achieved Black Belt in Karate, which took dedication
- → Ice Hockey & Ice Skating
  - Completed up to UK Skate level 5 in ice skating and level 6 in ice hockey

#### Retail Assistant

Primark, Nottingham

As a Retail Assistant for this high street clothing company, my responsibilities included:

- Answering customer queries and maintaining quality customer service
- Ensuring items are restocked and displayed effectively
- Training new starters with their duties (till training, department training)

During my time at Primark, I gained skills and experience in teamwork, customer service/engagement and merchandising.

Reason for leaving: Found an apprenticeship at flybmi to begin my career

#### EDUCATION

The Redhill Academy Sixth Form, Nottingham	2016-2018
A-level Computer Science	В
A-level Mathematics	В
A-level Physics	D
AS Chemistry	В

#### The Redhill Academy, Nottingham

2013-2016

# QUALIFICATIONS

- ➤ Alison Diploma in C# Programming
- ➤ Google Digital Garage Fundamentals of Digital Marketing
- ➤ BCS Level 2 ECDL in IT Application Distinction\*

# DRIVING LICENSE

Holder of a clean UK manual & automatic driving license since  $22^{nd}$  Nov 2017.